<Texts>
    <Text id="About-Text">Passionate software engineer dedicated to making a positive impact. With a global perspective gained from experiences in France and Spain, I have diverse expertise spanning CAD, automotive industry, security, and IoT. Presently employed at Dassault Systèmes in Lyon, France.</Text>
    <Text id="About-Nav">About</Text>
    <Text id="Experience-Nav">Experience</Text>
    <Text id="Education-Nav">Education</Text>
    <Text id="Skills-Nav">Skills</Text>
    <Text id="Projects-Nav">Projects</Text>
    <Text id="ContactMe-Button">Contact Me</Text>
    <Text id="Download-Button">Download CV</Text>
    <Text id="SofwareEngineer-Title">Software Engineer</Text>
    <Text id="About-Title">About</Text>
    <Text id="ContactInfo-Title">Contact Information</Text>
    <Text id= "Language-Text">Spanish, French ,English</Text>
    <Text id= "Experience-Section">Experience</Text>
    <Text id= "Present-Date">08/2019 - Present</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareEngineer-Dassault">Software Engineer</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault">Electrical System Design app inside the CATIA portfolio of the 3DExperience platform from Dassault Systemes. Development of an innovative app that empowers manufacturers to automatically generate networks and electrical schemas directly from 3D Mockups.</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_1">C++ development for CAD and PLM applications to design electrical systems on Windows and Linux OS</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_2">CI/CD processes and enhance workflow efficiency through the development of tools using Python and Bash scripting</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_3">Develop UI elements utilizing web technologies to improve the user interface and overall user experience</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_4">Draft detailed technical software specifications and plan strategies for unit testing</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_5">Design software architecture with a primary focus on reusability, modular frameworks and enhanced flexibility</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_6">Define models for Model-Based Systems Engineering (MBSE) to contribute to the engineering process</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareEngineer-Continental">Software Engineer</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental">ECU software development to control a Direct Injection Engine inside the new E-Power technology for Nissan (combination of an internal combustion engine with a battery-driven electric motor).</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_1">Design of the system architecture for a real-time application. Focus on software reliability</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_2">Software development on C/C++ code conforming the AUTOSAR standard and following MISRA C guidelines</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_3">Python and Perl scripting to automate the creation of tests for both validation and non-regression purposes</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_4">Task management: task tracking, technical guidance and support to fellow employees</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_5">Develop a structured workflow for the internal code review process, supported by an automated system</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareEngineer-Collins">Software Engineering Intern</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Collins">Security application to control cameras using the detections made by the radar FMWC PSR-500. The application featured a user-friendly interface for system parameterization and monitoring, incorporating versatile drivers tailored to various camera protocols.</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Collins_1">C++ development using the QT framework for Windows and Linux OS</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Collins_2">Plan and specify validation tests to ensure the quality and reliability of software</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Collins_3">Create software mock-ups tailored for customer demonstrations</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareEngineer-Digi">Software Engineering Intern</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Digi">Final Degree Project “Connection of any device to the Cloud Service “Etherios”” at Digi International. Ethernet-based solution designed to offer cloud connectivity for UART-enabled devices, such as sensors or actuators.</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Digi_1">Study of cloud services, "Internet of Things", Big Data and M2M communications</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Digi_2">Software development in C. Concentrate on the development of communication sockets</Text>
    <Text id= "Education-Section">Education</Text>
    <Text id= "Degree-INP">Master's Degree</Text>
    <Text id= "DegreeEx-INP">Master of Engineering. Electrical and Electronic engineering</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-INP">Masters dedicated to Electrical Engineering part of a Spanish/France double Masters. For the final degree project I orientated towards software development with the project PSR-500 at Rockwell Collins</Text>
    <Text id= "Degree-UPNA">Master's Degree</Text>
    <Text id= "DegreeEx-UPNA">Master of Engineering. Electrical and Electronic engineering</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-UPNA">Masters dedicated to Electrical Engineering part of a Spanish/France double Masters. The masters dived into electrical and electronic engineering as well as management, mechanical engineering or thermodynamics.</Text>
    <Text id= "Degree-UR">Engineering Degree</Text>
    <Text id= "DegreeEx-UR">Electronic engineering degree</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-UR">Engineering degree focused on Electronic engineering. For the final degree project I orientated towards embedded software with the project “Etherios” at Digi International</Text>
    <Text id= "Skills-Section">Skills</Text>
    <Text id= "ProgrammingLanguages-Section">Programming Languages</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareApplications-Section">Software Applications</Text>
    <Text id= "Technologies-Section">Technologies</Text>
    <Text id= "DevelopmentMethodologies-Section">Development Methodologies</Text>
    <Text id= "Projects-Section">Projects</Text>
</Texts>