<Texts>
    <Text id="About-Text">Software engineer, lover of its work and willing to make a difference. I have international experience in countries such as France and Spain as well as in different domains such as CAD, automotive industry, security and IoT. Currently working for Dassault Systemes in Lyon, France.</Text>
    <Text id="About-Nav">About</Text>
    <Text id="Experience-Nav">Experience</Text>
    <Text id="Education-Nav">Education</Text>
    <Text id="Skills-Nav">Skills</Text>
    <Text id="Projects-Nav">Projects</Text>
    <Text id="ContactMe-Button">Contact Me</Text>
    <Text id="Download-Button">Download CV</Text>
    <Text id="SofwareEngineer-Title">Software Engineer</Text>
    <Text id="About-Title">About</Text>
    <Text id="ContactInfo-Title">Contact Information</Text>
    <Text id= "Language-Text">Spanish, French ,English</Text>
    <Text id= "Experience-Section">Experience</Text>
    <Text id= "Present-Date">08/2019 - Present</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareEngineer-Dassault">Software Engineer</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault">Electrical System Design app inside the CATIA product of the 3DExperience platform.</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_1">C++ development for CAD and PLM applications to design electrical systems on Windows and Linux OS</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_2">CI/CD management. Tools development in python and bash to improve process</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_3">Development of UI elements based on web technologies</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_4">Draft of technical software specifications and unit testing planning</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_5">Software architecture design focused on re-usability and modules/frameworks</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Dassault_6">Model definition for MBSE engineering</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareEngineer-Continental">Software Engineer</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental">AKKA Technologies on behalf of Continental Automotive France SAS. ECU software development to control a Direct Injection Engine (E-Power technology for Nissan).</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_1">Design the system architecture for a real-time application. Focus on software reliability</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_2">Software development on C/C++ code conforming the AUTOSAR standard</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_3">Scripting (python and perl) to create automatic tests for validation and non-regression</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_4">Team management, AKKA for Continental. Technical orientation and support of other employees</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Continental_5">Creation of software tools to help with task tracking and planning</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareEngineer-Collins">Software Engineering Intern</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Collins">Security application to control cameras using the detections made by the radar FMWC PSR-500</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Collins_1">C++ development using the QT framework for Windows and Linux OS</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Collins_2">Planning and specification of validation tests</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Collins_3">Software mock-ups for customer demos</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareEngineer-Digi">Software Engineering Intern</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Digi">Final Degree Project “Connection of any device to the Cloud Service “Etherios”” at Digi International.</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Digi_1">Study of cloud services, "Internet of Things", Big Data and M2M communications</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-Digi_2">Software development in C. Focus on communication socket development</Text>
    <Text id= "Education-Section">Education</Text>
    <Text id= "Degree-INP">Master's Degree</Text>
    <Text id= "DegreeEx-INP">Master of Engineering. Electrical and Electronic engineering</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-INP">Masters dedicated to Electrical Engineering part of a Spanish/France double Masters. For the final degree project I orientated towards software development with the project PSR-500 at Rockwell Collins</Text>
    <Text id= "Degree-UPNA">Master's Degree</Text>
    <Text id= "DegreeEx-UPNA">Master of Engineering. Electrical and Electronic engineering</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-UPNA">Masters dedicated to Electrical Engineering part of a Spanish/France double Masters. The masters dived into electrical and electronic engineering as well as management, mechanical engineering or thermodynamics.</Text>
    <Text id= "Degree-UR">Engineering Degree</Text>
    <Text id= "DegreeEx-UR">Electronic engineering degree</Text>
    <Text id= "Text-UR">Engineering degree focused on Electronic engineering. For the final degree project I orientated towards embedded software with the project “Etherios” at Digi International</Text>
    <Text id= "Skills-Section">Skills</Text>
    <Text id= "ProgrammingLanguages-Section">Programming Languages</Text>
    <Text id= "SoftwareApplications-Section">Software Applications</Text>
    <Text id= "Technologies-Section">Technologies</Text>
    <Text id= "DevelopmentMethodologies-Section">Development Methodologies</Text>
    <Text id= "Projects-Section">Projects</Text>
</Texts>